我们要充分利用framework(框架)为我们提供的条件来创建我们的
We'll take advantage of what the framework offers in order to build our
SettingsActivity组件  由于我们要支持运行Gingerbread的设备
SettingsActivity. Since we're supporting Gingerbread devices,
我们会使用PreferenceActivity类  如果你想要支持的设备是运行Honeycomb或者更新的系统
we'll use a PreferenceActivity class. If you're targeting Honeycomb later,
那么你可以使用PreferenceFragment类
you'll want to use the PreferenceFragment class.
根据下面提供的要点来创建一个新的SettingsActivity类
Create a new SettingsActivity class from the gist provided below.
在AndroidManifest文件中注册这个新的Activity组件  你可以看到
Update the AndroidManifest to declare this new activity. You can see the
DetailActivity作为例子也在其中  如果你发现有API被废弃了
DetailActivity is declared as an example. If you see that APIs are deprecated,
没有关系  这是我们在使用PreferenceActivity的时候  为了兼容运行Gingerbread的设备
that's okay. That's a side effect of using PreferenceActivity, in order
而产生的副作用  在你为了最终的项目编写你的App的时候
to target Gingerbread devices. When you create your App for your final project,
你可以使用Android Studio中的向导功能创建新的SettingsActivity组件
you can use the wizard in Android Studio to create a new SettingsActivity.
向导功能为你创建的代码会向后兼容旧的系统
The code the wizard provides will make your app backward compatible,
这是通过使用PreferenceActivity和PreferenceFragment做到的
by using a combination of PreferenceActivity and PreferenceFragment.
我们为了学习的需要  只是提供了一个相对简单的实现
Our gist is meant to be a simplified version of that for learning purposes. So
晚些时候  你就能更好地理解向导究竟做了什么工作
later, you'd be able to understand better what the wizard is doing.
完成以后就勾选上这些选项吧
Check these items off when you're done.